Let's see what you missed this week in the Amandaverse.
I wanna congratulate all of you
on making it through 2020 again this year.
Yay for y'all and us.
Is it that we're just now like more aware
of the wackness of things
or is it that it just keeps on being wack?
We love some good news,
but you know that they had made the price of insulin
like some crazy amount of money
because it is such a necessary element
of so many people's lives and I'm hoping, you know,
a lot of you all out there who are diabetic,
you can breathe a sigh of relief.
So Benedict Cumberbatch is one of several British families
that are gonna be asked to pay reparations to Barbados
for actually owning slaves.
We love to see it.
It's gonna be time to pay up for quite a few.